First element.
What do we do?
for some reason there was a lack
of spatial power and we couldn't
conjure our incineration projectiles
and then the enemy launched
a large-scale attack 90 of the
demi-human unit 70 % of the
ogre archers and over 30 % of the
dark mage unit were destroyed.
For some reason?
Are you dense?
Someone used a massive formal art and
drained all the spatial power in the ravine!
But how can that be?
I can't even conjure
a spell of that scale!
Who do they have that is that powerful?
I'm not just so human.
I am not just so human.
I am just so human.
Welcome back!
You did well.
The enemy has retreated.
You guided us to victory.
No, Fanatio.
This battle is far from being over.
More sacred powers.
has collected in the ravine.
We must consume it with healing
arts before the enemy can absorb it.
Time is short, and we have yet
to face their dark knights?
and pugilists.
True.
All who are able, take
the wounded and fall back!
Priests, focus on healing until all
the spatial power has been depleted!
And keep watch for enemy movement!
I will go and give my
report to the commander.
Will you be alright here? Mm-hmm.
I could not have succeeded
without you, Amayori.
Eat your phil and get some rest.
You've earned it.
M 'lady...
Haldrie!
Have you been injured?
No.
Nothing major, at least.
But if I am being honest, I
would have preferred to perish.
What kind of talk is that?
Your troops look up to you,
and you have a duty to lead
them and fight to the very end.
And yet, as a leader, I have failed.
Not only did the goblins breach my ranks,
their commander was felled by Ser Renly.
How humiliating.
I betrayed your teachings
and your expectations of me.
To think I could be worthy
of her heart, her love.
How laughable!
I do not have the right to
call myself your disciple!
Of course you do.
I know you did all you could.
Can you not see how
much everyone needs you?
The troops under your command?
The citizens?
I, too, as a matter of fact.
Do you?
For my strength on the battlefield?
Nothing more.
Stop right there.
What business do you have here unarmed?
Your life is almost at its end.
I be Frugger.
I be chief of all Ogre.
Keep up your guard.
He is one of their council of ten.
I saw all.
Light and fire.
You conjure. Unleash.
Your power. Your luck.
You be priestess of light.
If take back with me end
of war ogre return to
planes priestess end of
war who told you this?
Come on now speak up m 'lady
this fiend is obviously stolen!
But milady he lies as you say i am
the priestess of light now then before
i go anywhere with you I wish to
know who it is that seeks me emperor
vector he say find priestess of
light he grant Wish to who catch and
bring to him and then ogre can go
home raise horses hunt bird and leave?
Surely you must despise me
do you not wish to avenge
your people i killed them
burden of strong Heavy
as they be strong i chief
my burden to protect kind
is why i have no choice i
catch you And take back!
May your soul return home.
Back to the Plains.
Emperor Vecta.
So the reason your strategy failed
and a thousand Dark Mages died
was because the enemy absorbed all
the spatial power before you could.
Did I understand that correctly? Yes.
Your Majesty.
I swear we had no idea they had
someone who could cast such an art.
Only the Pontifex, and she is dead.
Is there some other way to
replenish this power? Yes,
using spatial resources such
as rich land and sunlight,
but to generate enough power to destroy
the enemy, we would need ample amounts?
and unfortunately, there is little here.
Obviously.
In fact, I see no grass or trees at
all, and the sun set a while ago.
So tell me, what were you going to use
as a power source for your attack spell?
Well, each life has power, and during the
assault, as warriors from both sides died,
their expired lives filled the
air with spatial power. Ah.
Blood and Life
D .I .L.
Would 3,000 be sufficient? What?
Yes, Your Majesty.
That would be enough.
Priestess of light?
Yes.
I do not recall reading about this
person in any of the history books,
but whoever she may be, the emperor
of the Dark Territory is after her.
This emperor is the dark god Vecta.
A god walking among us?
I find that hard to believe.
All right, kid.
Let's say Vekta's back and running
things in the Dark Territory.
If what the Ogre said's true,
and Vecta's looking for this Priestess
of Light, and he thinks you're it,
how's that gonna affect where
this war goes from here?
The five tribes want the
resources of the human empire.
However, Vecta just wants
the Priestess of Light.
I have a plan.
I shall enter the Dark Territory,
then make my way to the edge of it.
If the Priestess of Light
is what Vecta wants,
then he will come after
me, with most of his army.
The troops he leaves behind
will be without leadership,
and you can wipe them out in the chaos.
Then, I shall make my way
to the World's End Altar.
Alright, once we're off the line,
I'll crank the FLA to a thousand.
Then, take Alice and head
to the World's End Altar.
I never heard of that place!
That's okay.
Just go out the eastern gate
and the altar's due south.
Perhaps if I go there.
All right.
But I'm sending a third of
our troops along with you.
Uncle, you cannot spare that
many just for my escort.
The enemy has more than 30,000 left.
They're not all going to chase you,
especially if you're the
only one running around.
If the plan is to get
them to split their ranks,
we gotta give them a big enough reason to.
You have a point.
I got one more condition for ya.
What is it?
The only way you're doing
this is if I come along.
Orc Chief Lil Pelon.
You will offer 3,000 lives so that my
Dark Mages can launch their attack spell.
You can't do that to us!
My tribe are warriors,
and we came here to fight!
You and your people failed, so why do
we have to pay for that with our lives?
This is an order from the Emperor.
Lil, we have no choice except
to obey His Majesty's orders.
I'd lend you.
If he needs 3,000 of our troops,
I'll offer my life and my clans.
I'll do it for him, and
for the honor of the Orc.
Lil, you know what I believe.
All souls go to heaven,
be it human or orc.
When we die, we go there.
And that's where I'll be waiting for you.
I know, Len, I know.
I'm sorry, I can't stop this.
You will assemble your troops
100 mils from the ravine.
3,000, not one less.
Do it now!
Right, move out!
Helltree.
Our goal is to split the enemy forces
and destroy the group that follows us.
After we pass through the
Eastern Gate, the Guard Unit,
the Priest Unit, and the
Supply Corps will head south.
If the terrain is favorable,
the troops will take position.
Until then, we Knights
will act as a diversion.
Return to your positions,
and prepare for battle!
System call, transfer human
unit durability, area to south,
generate umbral element, worm
Wormshape!
Long be to your tribe!
Glory be to the earth!
Lentu!
Damn humans.
Damn them all.
Curse on every one of them.
it can't be they are chanting a sacred
art uncle i used all the spatial
resources here there should not be enough
left to carry out a large-scale art
there is they're making it
what incredible power how magnificent
I just got word from our spotters.
There are Integrity Knights approaching.
This Deathworm attack spell can't
be blocked by sword or armor.
Those damned Integrity Knights
will be devoured alive.
Be patient.
Let them get closer. Hold. Hold.
Now! Fire!
We're gonna lure him away!
Pull up!
Damn it! No, kid!
Your sword won't work!
Huuuuhh!
Eldrie!
What are you doing, Eldrie?!
Divine serpent of yore, if you
are truly the king of snakes,
then you should have no trouble
devouring this pack of earthworms!
Release Recollection!
This way, you disgusting things!
No!
I shall not give up!
Not yet!
Lady Alice...
Albrea!
Altar!
Please, open your eyes!
Don't die!
You cannot leave me, not
like this, do you hear?
You're safe, m 'lady.
Yes, yes I am, thanks to you.
Don't go, I meant it
when I said I need you.
Do not cry, m 'lady.
You must think of those who need you.
They are all that matter now, not I.
I have behaved so selfishly.
I thought I could have you all to myself.
That does not matter.
Just stay.
You are my disciple.
I will give you whatever you wish.
No, I have all that I need.
Paltrier! Paltrier!
Do not cry.
Mug...
Furn.
Eldrie.
I swear to you, they shall
pay for what they've done!
Amayori, Takiguri, charge the enemy.
No!
It can't be!
At that priority level,
the Death Worms should
have easily devoured
the Integrity Knights
and the ground troops!
What kind of art did
those rotten humans use?
Retreat!
Hurry, fall back!
Burn them!
Burn them all!
Enhance armament.
No!
I can't die!
Not here, not like this!
I'm going to be the empress!
I'm supposed to become
the ruler of this world!
My lady, we've done nothing wrong!
System called!
I am Alice, Integrity Knight!
Alice Synthesis 30!
I am the proxy of the three
goddesses who protect this realm!
I am the Priestess of Light,
and whoever dares defy me shall
know the fury of my power!
Alice...
Alicia...
One day, even though I'm just calm.
Time to fall down!
A strong heart.
Two of them were just so dry.
Thank you so much
for being here.
If you're alone, you'll
be able to live alone.
It doesn't matter if
you don't love anyone.
I don't want you to be able to do it.
It's your voice, it's your voice.
It's my dream.